I did a video that showed Mayor Muriel Bowser of D.C. continuing to be the mouthpiece of the administration in their occupation of D.C.
And the overwhelming amount of responses that I got from people saying, well, she's just doing what she has to do to keep her position was alarming to me.
Because I want to know from you guys, do you think that that's noble?
Do you think her keeping her position at the cost of the people that she was put in position to serve is noble?
Because you're saying it not simply just as a fact, but as an excuse that is excusable.
And then I ask you, so if she is in said position and she is capitulating to everything that the opposition is doing, and she has been doing this for her entire time in office, what is the purpose of her being in that position?
I'll never understand why people think as long as the person in power is black, it's still valuable to black folks.
No, if a person in power is black, and they are harmful to black folks, then they are only useful to the oppressor.
They are literally being used as a weapon against black folks, who for the record, have been one of the most useful resources of this nation.
Because right now, what they are doing is using immigrants to be the free labor, and they're using black minds to do the labor of convincing a whole nation that slavery is okay if it's not them.
Support a real one.